

PROFILE

Hello, my name is Paula Valencia I'm an Interactive Media Designer from Colombia. I describe myself as a perseverant person, I learning new things and my passion is to learn from Japanese culture.

During my professional path, I have developed skills that make me able to work with User Experience, Graphic Design, Web Design, App Development, and Video Editing.

My main social skills are composed of high adaptability, teamwork, and

CONTACT ME

- +57 304 590 2690
- @ tona.valencia@hotmail.com
- http www.tonavalencia.github.io

EDUCATION

PLATZI 2020

UX Process Management February 2020 Video Game Design February 2020 Flutter August 2020

ICESI UNIVERSITY 2018 **Interactive Media Designer July 2013 - August 2018**

MITSUE-LINKS CO .LTD 2018 **UX Research Internship April 2018 - July 2018**

NIHON UNIVERSITY 2017 **International Exchange Student** September 2016 - February 2017

EXPERIENCE

CORPORACIÓN TALENTUM 2020

Unity Game Developer July 2019 - Present Game developer in a corporation that works with the Government of El Valle. With my team, we develop educational games with the purpose to encourage the use of technology in an educational environment for populations with

low resources.

FOSFENOS MEDIA - EL SALVADOR'S MINISTRY OF EDUCATION 2019

> Interactive Desginer March 2019 - May 2019 Web development and design for the brand new animated program Historias en Juego presented on the educational television channel TATUKATV. http://tatukatv.sv/historias-en-juego

MITSUE- LINKS CO. LTD

2018 UX Research Intern April 2018 - July 2018 Research intern for user experience. Worked with user tests, project reports, blog writings, cultural

> differences, and research findings. https://www.mitsue.co.jp/english/global_ux/blo g/201805/16_1800.html

IOL COLOMBIA

Main Designer - July 2015 / July 2017 Responsible for the design of brand, development and web design, graphic design of promotional pieces, management of social network.

LANGUAGES

2017





